twi.la 2010-04-04

# Privacy Policy | Tweet.me.it - we'll make it shorter

This web site has agreed to notify you of:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site
  * The organization collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under tweet.me.it's control
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### Information Collection & Use

tweet.me.it is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. tweet.me.it collects information from our users in several places on our site.

### Registration

In order to interact with this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to provide the user with the ability to log into the site to make additions or deletions to their account.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We also use your IP address to identify your account.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that tweet.me.it is not responsible for the privacy practices and content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
